Contact

vodemu@aol.com (Home) vodemu@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/violet-odemu-9053a846 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ACLS

BLS

Critical Care

Certifications

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

TNCC

Violet Odemu

Staff Nurse at El Camino Health

San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

Experienced Critical Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical-Surgical, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Intensive Care, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's of Nursing focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from St. John's College.

Experience

El Camino Health Staff Nurse June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months) Mountain View, California

Kaiser Permanente Staff Nurse October 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Regional Medical Center of San Jose Critical Care Registered Nurse IV October 2012 - May 2019 (6 years 8 months)

FlexCare Medical Staffing
Traveling Nurse - Critical Care
May 2012 - October 2013 (1 year 6 months)

AMN Healthcare
Traveling RN
June 2011 - March 2013 (1 year 10 months)

trustaff
Traveling RN

April 2011 - October 2012 (1 year 7 months)

St. Francis Health Center Medical Laboratory Scientist - Generalist February 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 3 months)

Stormont-Vail HealthCare
Registered Nurse - Trauma Surgical ICU
December 2009 - April 2011 (1 year 5 months)

Passavant Area Hospital
Registered Nurse
March 2009 - September 2009 (7 months)

St. John's Hospital 6 years Phlebotomy Supervisor 2008 - 2009 (1 year)

Medical Technologist January 2003 - 2008 (5 years)

Education

St. John's College

Bachelor's of Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2007)

St. John's School of Clinical Laboratory Science

Clinical Laboratory Science, Clinical Laboratory Science/Medical Technology/

Technologist · (2002 - 2003)

Western Illinois University

Clinical Laboratory Science, Clinical/Medical Laboratory Science/Research and Allied Professions · (1999 - 2003)